









About

Highly organized and detail-oriented Computer Engineering student with 1+ years experience in **Python** from the University of Bojnord with relevant knowledge in **RESTful APIs**, **SQL** & **NoSQL** databases, and excellent **problem-solving** skill and **teamwork** ability. Looking for a remote **entry-level position** as a **Django Back-end Developer**.



Experience

Front-end & Back-end developer

Freelancer Shiraz, Fars, Iran

10/2021 - 04/2022 (6 months)

- A paid membership website for forex signal based on Django, Bulma and Javascript https://technical144.com (unavailable)
- Build a remote licensing system based on **Django** for Metatrader expert https://bott-indicator.com

Instructor of Python programming online course

University of Bojnord

07/2021 - 09/2021 (2 months)

 An online Python training course from elementary to intermediate in a project-oriented manner under the supervision of University of Bojnord

Student Intern

Fars Science and Technology Park (FSTP)

Shiraz, Fars, Iran

Shiraz, Fars, Iran

06/2021 - 09/2021 (3 months)

Gain experience working with PyQt, JavaFX, and building RESTful APIs by Django, Flask base on Docker

Teacher assistants

University of Bojnord

Bojnord, North Khorasan, Iran

- Teaching Assistant of Python for Data Science Course (Semester 8)
- Teaching Assistant of Advanced Programming Course (Semesters 3, 7, 8)
- Teaching Assistant of Fundamentals of Computer and Programming Course (Semester 7)



Education

B.Sc Computer Engineering

University of Bojnord

Bojnord, North Khorasan, Iran

2018 - Present (4 years)

(One of the top 10 students among 84 students)

- Fundamentals of Computer Science, Networks and Database
- Programming Languages (Java, Python, C++)



Skills

Knowledgeable Python Django Web Scraping

Familiar Django Rest Framework(DRF) Flask Javascript HTML/CSS PostgreSQL MongoDB Redis

Linux Git Scrum Clean Code Design Patterns

Languages Persian (Native) English (Intermediate)

Soft Skills Time management Effective communication Conflict management Teamwork Google Searching



Member of ICPC club (Ravens)

University of Bojnord 2018 - 2020 (2 years) Bojnord, North Khorasan, Iran

• A club to organize and synergize students' programming activities. We hold weekly ICPC prep sessions for 20+ students who are passionate about programming.

We participated in the ACM competitions:

- o Islamic Azad University of yadegar emam Shahr Rey
- UBCOM3, UBCOMP4 (University of Bojnord)
- Accept5 (Sadjad University of Technology)

Students' Scientific Association representative of the Department of Computer Engineering

University of Bojnord

Bojnord, North Khorasan, Iran

2019 - 2021 (2 years)

• As the liaison between students and the university faculty and staff, I work to address educational, social and financial challenges faced by the student body. Planned and held several student programming workshops and friendly meetings.